

Contacts

E: leroyliudmyla@gmail.com

in: linkedin.com/in/liudmylaleroy

Tech Skills

- MS Office(Excel)
- Tableau
- R
- SQL
- BigQuery
- PowerBl
- Python
- ETL
- Data Modeling
- Data-driven Decision Making
- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- GIT
- GitHub
- Hosting
- API
- AJAX
- Responsive
- Figma
- SEO
- Flexbox
- Bootstrap
- VS
- QA-engineer
- React.is
- 1-C.Accounting

Soft Skills

- High emotional intelligence
- Strong logical thinking
- Responsibility
- · Leadership qualities
- Creativity
- Scrum
- Aaile
- Teamwork

Languages

Data Analyst Manager Front-End Developer

from Ukraine based in Antwerp, Belgium

Liudmyla Leroy

Hike children and numbers.

As a mathematician, I see the beauty of this world.

As a physicist, I see the foundations of existence.
As a teacher, I understand the power of knowledge and development.

As a programmer, I create, fill, develop, get to know this world even more. As an economist and analyst, I analyze everything, make it easy to understand and help make important conclusions and plans.

As a person, I strive to improve this world.

What am I looking for?

I am looking for a team of like-minded people with whom I will be comfortable working and doing good and useful things.

Now I would prefer data analytics, business intelligence or programming. And also the remote format of work.

But I also like to teach and organize.

What I can do for you?

As an economist, founder and manager, I worked in the field of:

- -logistics (road transport),
- -construction (highways, metal-plastic structures, external and internal repairs of buildings),

-education (lessons of mathematics, computer science, geography and astronomy, fashion show lessons, acting skills, design and tailoring, photo posing).

I produced ideas, organized processes, conducted active communication with partners, drew up contracts, statutory documents, developed tariff grids for salaries, calculated calculations, formed the price, forecasted the economic success of the company's possible actions. Therefore, I can do data analysis perfectly based on my extensive experience, including with Excel and Google tools. And also with new skills for working with SQL, R, Tableau, PowerBI, Python. Act quickly and accurately in critical situations.

As a web developer, I can create sites using HTML, CSS and frameworks, adapt them for different devices. Acquaintance with Figma. I study JavaScript hard. My university knowledge of algorithms, basics of Java helps a lot. I love if-else, I know operators, loops, arrays well. I work with API. I know Vanilla JavaScript better and I'm learning React.

Portfolio

https://portfolio-liudmyla-leroy.netlify.app

Work Experience

Data Analyst, Business Intelligence, Front-End Developer in Workshops and Pet Projects

August 2022 - until now | Online

- I have research and data visualization using spreadsheets, R, BigQuery, Tableau, PowerBI and Google Slides. Projects in my portfolio.
- I made several projects using HTML, CSS, JavaScript Vanilla and React, Flexbox, Bootstrap. Also with work at Figma, created modal windows. Some sites are adapted for different devices and with SEO optimization. Projects in my portfolio.

Volunteer in City of Antwerp

April 2022 - December 2022 | Belgium

- Creation and organization of a temporary school for about 100 and organization of summer offers for about 150 Ukrainian children with temporary protection in Belgium.
- Management

UKrainian ianguage Native language

Russian language Like native

English language Intermediate

Dutch languageBasic level

French language Basic level

German language Basic level

- Generation and implementation of ideas in the team
- Teamwork in new extreme conditions
- · Teaching children and adults
- Psychological support for children and parents, in particular in war conditions

Teacher, founder and manager in Schools

January 2011 - August 2022 | Ukraine, Belgium

- · Child care
- · Work with parents
- Creative Development
- Teaching mathematics
- Psychological support for children and parents, in particular in war conditions

Chairman of the Board, a member of the NGO, project coordinator, a member of the Board in Public organizations "Mother's Territory" and "Family Development".

July 2012 - February 2022 | Ukraine

- Management
- Coordination
- Planning

Private entrepreneur in Private entrepreneur

August 2005 - February 2022 | Ukraine

- Personnel Management
- Effective planning
- · Responsibility
- Organization Skills
- Work with photo and video editors

Accountant in The Red Cross Society of Ukraine

April 2019 - November 2020 | Ukraine

- Work in 1C and Microsoft Office
- Work with government agencies

Leading economist in OJSC Pivdenzahidshlyakhbud

October 2001 - July 2005 | Ukraine

- Work planning
- Analysis of the enterprise
- Formation of prices and salaries
- Work with partners
- Work with government
- Work in 1C and in the state program based on MS-DOS
- Budgeting

Education

Coursera

Google Business Intelligence Specialization

September 2023 - November 2023 | Online learning in English

Coursera

Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate

June 2023 - August 2023 | Online learning in English

SheCodes

Front-end Developer

August 2022 - April 2023 | Online learning in English

Kharkiv Financial and Economic Institute Secretary-referent

September 1998 - July 1999 _I Ukraine

Vinnytsia State Pedagogical University. M. Kotsyubynsky Specialist. Teacher of mathematics and physics, IT

September 1993 - July 1998 _I Ukraine